tweetree.com 2012-05-03

# Tweetree - Privacy Policy

## Tweetree Privacy Policy

This is the web site of Tweetree, a website created by [Draconis Software, LLC.](http://www.draconis.com/)

Our postal address is  
444 Washington St, Suite 202  
Woburn, MA 01801  
We can be reached via e-mail at [info@draconis.com](mailto:info@draconis.com) or you can reach us by telephone at (617) 812-1701

For each visitor to our Web page, we collect the IP address of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as Twitter message content).

With regards to security: We take reasonable precautions to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We employ electronic and physical safeguards, including maintaining servers in a secure datacenter, and installing firewalls, encryption, and other software. Your Twitter login and password is transmitted to the Twitter API, and is used for no other purpose. Access to Tweetree servers is restricted to only those Draconis Software employees requiring it to perform their duties.

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

With respect to cookies: Like many websites, we use cookies to record session information such as account registrations.

We do not send any emails of any kind to users. For emails like forgotten password reminders, users are directed to Twitter.com.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes. We suggest that you regularly check this Privacy Policy for changes.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, how we use your personal information, or any other tweetree-related questions, please contact us.
